there's one thing you should know about
me I specialize in a very specific type
of
security subconscious
security you're talking about
dreams Mr car has a job offer he would
like to discuss with you kind a work
placement not
exactly we create the world of the
dream we bring the subject into that
dream and they fill it with their
secrets then you break can ins Ste it
well it's not strictly speaking legal
it's called
Inception I'm
ready I think I found a way
home and this last job that's how I get
there dreams feel real while we're in
them it's only when we wake up that we
realize something was actually
strange this was your responsibility we
are not prepared for
this dreams
collapsing I have it under control
I'd hate to see out of
control you mustn't be afraid to dream a
little bigger darling